https://www.jrosspub.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

J. Ross Publishing Inc.
browse titles
Checkout
Now Accepting
0 items: $0.00
Call us:
Home
BusinessBusiness AnalysisCorporate StrategyEducationEntertainmentFinanceInnovation & Product DevelopmentIT and Software BooksOperations ManagementProject and Program Management BooksStudy Guides and Test BanksSupply Management and Procurement BooksTextbooks and Study GuidesArchitectureAcoustics BooksConstruction BooksDesign BooksTextbooksEngineeringCivil Engineering BooksEngineering ClassicsGeneral Engineering BooksGeotechnical BooksTextbooksScienceAcoustics BooksEnvironmental Science BooksTechnology Books
Search:
Search
Home
/
Privacy Policy
J. Ross Publishing Privacy Policy
J. Ross Publishing recognizes the importance of protecting the information collected from Users in the operation of this website, and takes reasonable steps to maintain the security, integrity, and privacy of any information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By submitting your information to J. Ross you consent to the practices described herein.
J. Ross will seek to ensure that any identifiable personal information it collects during the registration and purchasing processes will be adequate, relevant, and not excessive for purposes of operating this website or any of the services operated hereunder and it will be kept accurate and up-to-date based on information provided. Except as expressly provided herein or, unless we have received your consent, J. Ross will not disclose any personal information identifying users to any third party except where necessary in connection with services provided by appropriate intermediaries, who will be required to comply with the confidentiality provisions of this policy. In addition, J. Ross may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties in order to comply with the law or requests by law enforcement agencies, to enforce our Terms and Conditions, or to protect the rights, property or safety of our website, users, or others. In the event that all or substantially all of the business or assets of J. Ross are sold or otherwise assigned to another entity, personally identifiable information may be transferred to such entity. Personal information and any other communications or information supplied to J. Ross may be used by J. Ross for internal business and research purposes and to help enhance and develop our website.
If you provide J. Ross with a physical or email address, you may receive periodic mailings (e-mailings) from J. Ross. On occasion, J. Ross may make its physical mailing address lists available to other companies who it believes may have products and services of interest to J. Ross's customers. J. Ross will not make your email address available to third parties except as described in the previous paragraph or, on occasion, to the authors of specific books you have purchased on our website or material you have downloaded from the WAV (Web Added ValueTM) section of our website.  If you do not wish to receive mailings (e-mailings) from J. Ross, its imprints, or third-party organizations, please let us know via phone, fax, mail, or email at customerservice@jrosspub.com or simply unsubscribe from any email you receive.
J. Ross may disclose to carefully chosen third parties navigational and transactional information in the form of anonymous, aggregate usage statistics (including "page views" on this website and the products herein) and demographics but only in forms that do not reveal a User's identity or confidential information, except as required by law, as needed in connection with legal proceedings, or unless we have received your consent.
Cookies are small bits of information that a website transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer's hard disk so that the website can remember who you are when you return. Cookies remember information about your activities on the site and enable the operator of the site to make your visits more enjoyable or customize your experience. We may use cookies in a variety of ways, such as to collect information to help us learn things like what kinds of customers our site attracts, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. We don't use cookies to collect and store individually identifiable information. You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely.
You should be aware that identifiable personal information--such as your name or e-mail address--that you voluntarily disclose that is accessible to other Users (e.g. on bulletin boards or in chat areas) could be collected and disclosed by others. J. Ross cannot take any responsibility for such collection and disclosure.
Please note that J. Ross's Privacy Policy is reviewed periodically. J. Ross reserves the right to modify its Privacy Policy at any time without notice. Any changes to the policy will be posted on this page. Your continued use of this website will be deemed conclusive acceptance of such modification. Any comments or questions concerning this policy should be addressed by entering your comments through our Contact Us page. If at any point you wish to access your personal information to (1) change your preferences, (2) review the accuracy, or (3) correct, supplement or modify your information, you may either select the Contact Us page as set forth above, or make in a written request to J. Ross Publishing Inc., 151 N. Nob Hill Rd., #476, Plantation, FL 33324. If you wish to modify your shopping account, you can do it directly in the My Account section of our website.
Publish With Us
Our Publishing Program
Submit a Proposal
Manuscript Preparation
Instructors
Customer Resources
Individuals
Booksellers
